<?xml version="1.0"?>
<map>
	<room name='TARDIS' dir_name='the'>You and Clare are in the TARDIS, it seems quiet after what happened recently. The doctor (you) intigued, thinks...

"Clara's state of mind seems to have changed. Perhaps she's still getting used to the *new* doctor.
After all, he didn't have these large attack eyebrows and he never left her. Maybe I have to change..."

Meanwhile, the TARDIS starts to spin out of the time vortex, everything's shaking, Clara holds on 
tightly and shouts "What are you doing Doctor?!". Most of the light vanishes except that of the 
TARDIS' orange glowing console. You go to grab your just-visible sonic screwdriver but you've 
lost it. You and the sonic screwdriver are slowly moving in zero gravity towards the top of the
TARDIS console. You need the sonic screwdriver to gain control of the TARDIS. 

The console controls aren't working.<item name='sonic_screwdriver' name_type='' use='true' give='false' drop='false' take='true' weight='20G'>A very useful tool in tricky situations</item>
<item name='phone' name_type='' use='false' give='true' drop='true' take='true' weight='150G'>A cyberman head</item>
<character name='Clara'>The impossible girl<item name='phone' name_type='' use='false' give='true' drop='true' take='true' weight='150G'>Low battery</item></character>
	</room>
	<room name="Queen's Arcade" dir_name='the'></room>
	<room name="Sainsbury's" dir_name=''></room>
	<room name='Trevithick Building' dir_name='the'></room>
	<room name='Refectory' dir_name='the'></room>
	<room name='Reception' dir_name=''>Reception is a nice place to live if you're a receptionist.
Receptionists are cool.<exit direction='south' room='Toilets'/>
		<exit direction='west' room='Staircase'/>
		<item name='biscuits' name_type='pack' use='true' give='true' drop='true' take='true' weight='500G'>A pack of biscuits</item>
	</room>
	<room name='C/2.04-5' dir_name=''><character name='Kerill Seridikov'>Some say he'sas persistant as a robot<item name='charger' name_type='' use='true' give='false' drop='true' take='true' weight='20G'>Useful for portable devices</item></character></room>
	<room name="Robs' Room" dir_name=''></room>
	<room name='Toilets' dir_name='the'>A strange lingering smell has been present for quite some time<exit direction='down' room='Sewers'/></room>
	<room name='Staircase' dir_name='the'>There are stairs. That's it.</room>
	<room name='Sewers' dir_name='the'>A stench is all you can smell and it sticks to your clothes like the smell of tobacco</room>
</map>